{
	"list": [
		{"question":"pA_question1","answer":"pA_answer1"},
		{"question":"pA_question2","answer":"pA_answer2"},
		{"question":"pA_question3","answer":"pA_answer3"},
		{"question":"pA_question4","answer":"pA_answer4"},
		{"question":"pA_question5","answer":"pA_answer5"},
		{"question":"pA_question6","answer":"pA_answer6"},
		{"question":"pA_question7","answer":"pA_answer7"},
		{"question":"pA_question8","answer":"pA_answer8"},
		{"question":"pA_question9","answer":"pA_answer9"},
		{"question":"pA_question10","answer":"pA_answer10"},
		{"question":"pA_question11","answer":"pA_answer11"},
		{"question":"pA_question12","answer":"pA_answer12"},
		{"question":"pA_question13","answer":"pA_answer13"},
		{"question":"pA_question14","answer":"pA_answer14"},
		{"question":"pA_question15","answer":"pA_answer15"},
		{"question":"pA_question16","answer":"pA_answer16"},
		{"question":"pA_question17","answer":"pA_answer17"},
		{"question":"pA_question18","answer":"pA_answer18"},
		{"question":"pA_question19","answer":"pA_answer19"},
		{"question":"pA_question20","answer":"pA_answer20"},
		{"question":"pA_question21","answer":"pA_answer21"}
	]
}